freedesignfile.com 2019-07-01

# Freedesignfile Privacy Policy

Freedesignfile Privacy Policy explains the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information by Freedesignfile, located at freedesignfile.com.

Freedesignfile has implemented all reasonable measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception or processing of personal information that we control. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Freedesignfile and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its third parties.

**USE OF INFORMATION**

Profile information you submit to Freedesignfile will be available to visitors of the website and limited pieces of information may be made available to third party search engines. Freedesignfile may send you website-related announcements from time to time. Generally, you may opt out of such emails by unsubscribing to our email updates.

Freedesignfile may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is  
1) permitted by you  
2) reasonably necessary to offer the service or  
3) legally requested as we might be required to disclose user information in compliance with applicable laws.

We may use third parties to facilitate our operations, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to process payments for products or services, to offer an online job application process, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these activities.

Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the free vector-specified purposes.

We let you choose to share information with marketers or electronic commerce providers through on-site offers. We may offer stores or provide services jointly with other websites, brands or companies.

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**

Advertisements that appear on Freedesignfile are sometimes served directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and web beacons to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked.

Freedesignfile does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on Freedesignfile unless you choose to share it with them.

**SECURITY**

Freedesignfile takes appropriate precautions to protect our users’ information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information (such as Paypal password or credit card number), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

**CHANGING OR REMOVING INFORMATION**

Access and control over most personal information on Freedesignfile is readily available through the profile editing tools. Freedesignfile users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their Freedesignfile account may do so on the My Account page. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available.

**LINKS**

Freedesignfile may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

If you have any questions about this privacy. Please Contact Us.
